怎么 你现在是太阳了是吗
滋润万物是吧
扬克斯   1968年
迪克 人们已经认为女权主义是个肮脏的词了
Well, Dick, people already think feminism is a dirty word,
曼哈顿   1972年
所以我觉得 打不过就加入
so I say if you can't beat 'em, join 'em.
太油嘴滑舌了吗
Too glib?
太油嘴滑舌了
Too glib.
迪克 我一直觉得最好的真理都是赤裸裸的
Well, Dick, I've always found the best truths are naked ones.
这个很好
Oh, that is good.
道格 你去哪儿
Doug, where have you been?
道格是谁
- Who's Doug?
-麦琪快  -全告诉我
Maggie! Oh! - Tell me everything.
-如果你私奔 我会杀了  -你真高兴你能来
If you elope, I will kill you. - Oh, I'm so glad you made it.
我只要撒个小谎就可以逃避工作了
Well, I only had to tell a little fib to get out of work.
我们还是要赶最后期限
Oh. - We're on deadline as always.
但我不可能错过你上迪克·卡维特的
But there was no way I was gonna miss you
-节目  -我知道
on Dick friggin' Cavett! - I know!
你能相信这有多难以置信
Can you believe how crazy--
我说 这一切发生得太快了
I mean, this has all happened so fast.
你很有名 而这仅仅是个开始
You are famous. And this is just the beginning.
他们让我住在广场酒店
You know, they put me up at the Plaza.
我的房间有三部电话
My room has three phones,
入口吊灯
this entryway chandelier,
还有回声
and its own echo.
我就知道你会
I always knew you would
凯旋回到纽约
come back to New York in triumph.
你的杂志 哇
Your magazine is-- wow.
-我不知道你是怎么做到的  -你了解我的
I do not how you pull it off. - Well, you know me.
我总觉得最好的真理总是赤裸裸的
I've always found the best truths are naked ones.
太好了 你应该就这么说
Oh, that is good! You should say that.
挺好的 对吧 我就用这个
It's good, right? I'm using that.
噢 贝琪呢
- Oh, and Betsy?
-高级编辑 从什么时候开始的  -说来话长
Senior editor? Since when? - That is a story.
格温娜维尔在斯塔登
So Guinevere was in Staden--
普里格小姐 你需要化妆
- Miss Prigger, you're needed in makeup.
Oh, Miss Prigger, you're needed in makeup.
停下
Stop it.
她是暖色调的 别给她用深色
- She's a summer. Don't put her in a plum.
谢谢
- Thank you.
你身上散发着加州的光芒
So you got that California glow.
你去过纽约吗
Ever been to New York?
如果不扩大自由和机会
- What is progress if not the expansion
什么才叫进步
of freedom and opportunity?
这就是越南想要的
That's all the Vietnamese want.
美国政府算老几啊 想阻止他们
Who's the US government to try and stop them?
乔斯林 你能过来一下吗
Hey, Joselyn, can you come here a sec?
你洗完碗后 可以
After you do the dishes, can--
五个鸡蛋
oof, five eggs?
她叫什么名字
What's her name?
在她之前那个走路怪怪的
Who was the blonde with the funny walk
金发女是谁
who was here before her?
-帕蒂  -哦对 帕蒂
- Oh, um, Patty - Yeah, Patty.
她以前能从那些鸟那里拿到更多的蛋
She used to get way more eggs out of those birds.
对不起
Oh, sorry.
我刚刚掌握了窍门
I'm just getting the hang of it.
是啊 鸡看得出来
Yeah, well, the chickens can tell.
这是斯文 他是新来的 他要用罗杰的房间
This is Sven. He's new. He'll be taking Roger's room.
为什么 罗杰怎么了
- Oh, why? What happened to Roger?
条子在我们的华尔街行动里砸了他的头
Pigs busted his head in at our Wall Street action.
他父母不得不从阿斯彭飞过来接他回家
Parents had to fly in from Aspen just to take him home.
天啊 太可怕了
Oh, God, that's awful.
我可不想惹什么麻烦
Um, I don't wanna cause any problems
但我的理解是这里的房间
but, um, my understanding was that rooms here
是根据资历分配的
were assigned based on seniority,
我还躺在储藏室的发霉床垫上呢
and I'm still on that moldy mattress in the pantry.
是的 但是斯文是欧洲人 所以
Yeah, but Sven's from Europe, so--
兄弟们我们不可能
- Guys, there's no way
走着这些东西去华盛顿广场
we're walking these things to Washington Square.
太大了 车装不下
Make them too big, they're not gonna fit in the van.
要是那些牛奶罐再大一点
- Those milk jugs get any bigger,
货车也装不下
they're not gonna fit in the van either.
坐下吧
Sit down.
再来一杯 比利 再来一杯
One more. Billy, please one more.
-拜托  -好的 再来一杯
Please. - All right. One more.
然后我就得上路了
Then I gotta hit the road.
醉鬼开车 没人能
Drive any drunker, ain't no autograph
-帮我摆脱麻烦  -对
getting me out of that trouble. - Right.
每一个奶子都是“适合”的 小姑娘
That's "fitty" for each titty, little lady.
继续喝 我也许能把我的孩子
Keep drinking, I might be able to get my baby
从公立学校里弄出来
out of public school.
我就是想安安静静欣赏一对漂亮的胸部
I'm just admiring a fine pair of breasts
她却要提她的孩子
and she's gotta mention her kid?
真的扫兴
Talk about a boner bomb. - Yeah.
但是我还是喜欢 喜欢得发硬
Still, I'd tax that. Hard.
这是我们
See, that's a flavor
目前在杂志上没有的风格
that we don't currently have at the magazine.
我看到了人与时刻之间的完美风暴 比利
I'm seeing the perfect storm between man and moment, Billy.
我不知道 道格
I don't know, Doug.
一方面
On the one hand,
展示我的老弟 那是纯比利·布伦森
showing my hog, that's pure Billy Brunson.
经典历史最佳
Classic GOAT.
另一方面 我不喜欢
On the other, I don't like the idea
-基佬们向我跑来  -这本杂志可不是
of fairies beating off to me. - Well, this magazine is not
给同性恋群体
for the homosexual community.
这是女性向的
It's for women.
-是吗  -很多女人
- Yeah? - A lot of them.
我刚和西格拉姆开完会
I just got out of a meeting with Seagram's.
本来不想这么说的 但底特律已经在三号
I wasn't gonna say this, but I got Detroit
四号和五号线上了 好吗
on lines three, four, and five, okay?
如果你在想比利·布伦森
And if you're thinking about what comes next
在足球比赛之后会感什么
for Billy Brunson after football,
就是发表这个
this launches that.
你们为什么说做那些女性解放的废话
Why y'all gotta do all that women's lib crap?
在巴马 我们让他们金发碧眼长大成安静的人
Down in Bama, we grow 'em blonde and quiet.
那就拿回麦克
So take back the mic.
你上过几次《体育画报》
I mean, how many times you been on the cover
的封面
of "Sports Illustrated"?
-6次吗  -7次
- Six? - Seven.
也许是时候宣布新消息了 比利
- Maybe it's time to make some new news, Billy.
你想让你前妻
You want that ex-wife of yours
躲不掉你吗
to be unable to escape your face.
老沃伦·比蒂被我揍了一顿后
OI' Warren Beatty dumped her quick
很快就甩了她
after I whopped his ass.
我告诉你 我不讨厌女人 道格
I'm gonna tell you, I don't hate women, Doug.
我知道 比利
- Oh, I know that, Billy.
这是我最欣赏你的一点
It's one of the things I admire most about you.
但如果某个电影明星上了我的前任
But I might punch out the occasional movie star
我可能会揍他一顿
if he plows my ex.
我申请了限制令
I framed the restraining order.
我们为什么不把它刊登在杂志上
Now, why don't we publish it in the magazine?
我可以扮成《雌雄大盗》里的克莱德
I could pose like Clyde from Bonnie and Clyde.
-那倒挺好  -给你把汤米的
- That'd be a nice ol' dig. - Give you a Tommy gun
-枪拿着  -汤米的枪
- to hold onto. - Tommy gun?
兄弟 就我裤兜里东西
Brother, with what I'm packing,
你不需要别的枪了
you ain't gonna need no other gun.
奶酪开始冒泡了
Ooh, this cheese is starting to bubble.
进来
Get in here.
毕加索都不如我会切面包丁
Picasso's got nothing on my bread cubes.
烈酒休息时间 每人拿点龙舌兰酒
- Shot break! Everyone grab some tequi-qui.
《风骚女子》现在是黄金期 宝贝
"Minx" is primetime, baby.
说得好
- Whoo! - Yes!
好酒
Mmm. That's the good stuff. - Mm-hmm.
蒂娜小姐 我知道你知道芝士火锅叉在哪儿
Now, Miss Tina, I know you got fondue forks somewhere.
储藏室
- Pantry. - Ah.
吸草时间
Grass break!
好吧 在你变得太激动之前
- Okay, before you get too excited,
我不会让你嗑药的
there will be no acid break... - Aww.
-我说今晚  -这些是什么
This evening. - What are these?
没什么 我爸爸送的
- Nothing. My dad sent them.
首先 你爸爸死了
Well, first of all, your dad's dead.
其次 你为什么把
Secondly, why are you hiding
鬼爸爸的花藏在储藏室
ghost dad's flowers in the pantry?
我错过了吸草时间吗
Did I miss grass break?
-书店比尔吗  -没谁
- Bookstore Bill? - It's nobody.
女孩就不能给自己买些玫瑰吗
Can't a girl buy herself some roses?
来吧 你一定要告诉我们
Come on. You have to tell us.
-是你的二表哥德里克吗  -他是我侄子
Is it your second cousin Derek? - He's my nephew.
-你说他很可爱  -他12岁
- You said he was cute. - He's 12.
天呐
Oh, my God.
道格
Doug?
又来
Again?
我告诉你 我在那该死的名单上
I'm telling you, man. I'm on the goddamn list.
我是杂志的出版人
I'm the publisher of the magazine.
-什么杂志  -《风骚女子》
- What magazine? - "Minx"!
我的女编辑上节目了
My lady editor is on the show.
是我 是我让她来的
And I-- and I am the reason she's here!
雷内蒂 不在名单上 我不能让你上去
Renetti, not on the list. I can't let you up.
-那就叫人来问问吧  -还有两分钟就要播出了
- Then call somebody, please. - It's two minutes to air.
没有人可以叫 你真倒霉
There's no one to call. You are out of luck.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
这儿 乔伊斯·普里格 她的伴儿
Right there. Joyce Prigger. Her plus two.
我就是那一团 第二团
I'm that little scribble. I'm the second scribble.
道格·雷内蒂
It's Doug Renetti.
哦 那也太小了
- Oh, wow. That is small.
好吧 进去吧
Yeah, go ahead. You're in.
《迪克·卡维特秀》
"The Dick Cavett Show."
在今晚的节目中我们请到了《风骚女子》杂志
On tonight's program, from "Minx" magazine,
编辑乔伊斯·普里格
Shh, shh, shh. - Editor Joyce Prigger.
你们大多数人现在
Most of you are aware by now
都知道妇女解放运动了
of the Women's Liberation Movement.
这个国家的很多女性都觉得
A lot of women in this country feel that,
社会对她们并不公平
well, society isn't exactly fair in its treatment of them.
她们厌倦了任人摆布
They're tired of being pushed around
她们希望事情有所改变
and they want things to change.
我想请一位对这一切
I'd like to bring out someone who has
有着独特观点的人
a somewhat unique point of view on all this.
她就是《风骚女子》杂志的编辑
She's the editor of "Minx" magazine,
如果你还没想清楚
which, if you haven't figured by now,
这本是女性向杂志
is not about semiaquatic, carnivorous mammals.
我也想给大家看看具体内容
I'd show you more,
但是如果我给了 我们节目就得被封了
but they'd cancel my show if I did.
这本杂志已经席卷了出版界
The magazine has taken the publishing world by storm,
几天之内第二期就卖光了
selling out its second issue in a matter of days.
但这是女权生义吗 还是色情
But is it feminist? Is it pornography?
或者两者兼而有之
Can it be both?
让我们找出答案 有请乔伊斯·普里格
Let's find out. Please welcome Joyce Prigger.
-欢迎  -你好谢谢
- Welcome. - Hello. Thank you.
看来你有一些粉丝啊
It seems like you've got some fans.
女人说话的时候声音会很大
Well, women can be loud when they use their voices.
-没那么可怕 是吧  -我什么都怕
- It's not so scary, is it? - Oh, I'm afraid of everything
我就是那种平均胆小鬼
I'm what'd you call an equal opportunity wimp.
别小看自己 迪克
Don't sell yourself short Dick.
有了我们的摄影师 连你都能成为风骚女子男模
With our photographer, even you coyld be a "Minx" man.
我认为这个世界还没有准备好看到我
I don't think the world is ready for that.
你们说呢 你们想一窥
What do you say? You wanna take a peek
迪克·卡维特的大门后吗
behind Dick Cavett's curtains?
好吧 好吧
Okay, okay
谁采访谁呢这是
Who's interviewing who here?
你想抢走我的饭碗吗女士
Are you gunning for my job, lady?
一个女性脱口秀主持人吗 我觉得是时候了
A female talk show host? I think it's about time.
如果我能做 是个人都能做吧
If I can do it, anyone can.
那么你到底是怎么
So how did you get into all this?
你的背景好像还蛮严肃的
You've got this straight-laced background.
-是呢  -去了不错的大学
- Mm-hmm. - Went to a fancy college.
作为一个小姑娘来说
I mean, as a little girl,
你有想过自己会上这档节目吗
is this where you imagined you'd be?
说实话迪克 我小时候的梦想是
- Well, Dick, in my childhood fantasy,
上沙利文秀 可不是来你这
I was on "Ed Sullivan," not here.
然后斯文给了我一个那种表情
And then Sven throws me this look like,
曼哈顿   1968年
不好意思 但我可没觉得对不起
"Oops, sorry but not sorry."
我赌100块 这个斯文
A hundred bucks this Sven character
-肯定是想上你  -他已经上过了
- tries to sleep with you. - Oh, he already did.
也许我也应该试试你这种生活
Maybe I'd like life on the commune.
你一天都撑不下去
You wouldn't last a single day.
真好闻
- Oh, you smell nice.
你给我买的洗发水
You bought my shampoo for me.
你都已经到这了
- I mean, you're here enough.
那你就一直走到毕格罗去给我买的吗
So you went all the way down to Bigelow to get it?
嗯 我让弗朗辛去的
Yeah-- sent Francine.
可怜的弗朗辛
Poor Francine.
我真的认为这件作品
You know, I really think this piece
会引起巨大的转变
is gonna cause a seismic shift.
没有人写反战运动中的
Nobody's writing about gender dynamics
性别动态
within the anti-war movement.
这些自由主义者对女性的态度很糟糕
These are good liberals who are just awful to women.
应该会让很多人都觉得不舒服
I think it's gonna make a lot of people uncomfortable.
希望不要像那个破烂的贮藏室床垫
- Not as uncomfortable
那么不舒服
as that ratty pantry mattress, I hope.
如果能写出一篇好文章
Listen, I am more than willing to suffer
我宁可忍受那个破床垫
for a good story.
我觉得你这个想法很有可能获得成功
My guess is you probably make it.
很有可能
Probably?
毋庸置疑
Indubitably.
然后我对这个议员说
And so I say to this councilwoman,
如果你要在我的照片上
"If you're gonna plaster my face all over the place
贴满恶魔角的标志
"on signs with devil horns, then at least
那至少用一张好看的吧
use a picture from my good side, you know?"
比如这样的
Oh, it's this one.
这么多负能量 都没能打倒你哈
And all that negativity, that didn't get to you?
估计很多人面对这种情况都会退缩了吧
A lot of people would just curl up and hide.
-这边 这边  -让一下
- Points. Points. - Oh, yeah, excuse me.
-不好意思 借过  -抱歉
- Excuse me. Sorry. - Sorry. Sorry.
-不好意思  -没看见你
- Excuse me. - Didn't see you.
让一下
Excuse me.
面对这些负面评论 你得有盔甲来保护自己
You've got this armor that protects you from critics.
这样就行
That'll do it.
第二点我想说的是
Secondly, I would say,
如果这让你很心烦那就别去想了
if it bothers you, don't buy it.
-你好  -抱歉
- Hello. - Oh, I'm sorry.
我以为这个
I thought this--
等等 我认识你
Wait a second. I recognize you.
你是西蒙妮·德 不是
You're Simone de B-- no.
那个法国名字我读不出来
That French name I can't pronounce.
不是你吗 杰曼·格里尔
That's not you? Germaine Greer?
接近了 她是澳洲人 也是我朋友
Closer. She's Australian and a friend.
维多利亚·哈奈特
Victoria Hartnett.
妇女参政受害者 我就知道
"Suffering Suffragettes." Yeah.
乔伊斯让我读过
Joyce had me read it.
-写的真不错  -谢谢
- I gotta say, not bad. - Oh, why, thank you.
没有什么比虚伪的赞美更糟糕的了
Nothing quite damns like faint praise.
道格·雷内蒂
Doug Renetti.
《风骚女子》的出版商
Publisher of "Minx." - Oh.
-那个可悲的色情文学家啊  -我觉得用卑鄙这词形容更合适
- The wretched pornographer. - I prefer "vile."
不过雷内蒂先生 我得给你点个赞
Well, I have to give you credit, Mr. Renetti.
我还没怎么见过有男人愿意自己退居幕后
I don't know a Iot of men who'd stand back here
然后让她上台去接受采访的
and let her be the one out there.
我只是个商人
- Oh, well, I'm a good businessman
而有她在我的生意才有的赚
and she's good for business.
她可是费了好大劲才走到今天这步
She's come a long way, that one.
是嘛 那她原来是什么样的
- Oh, and from where did she travel?
我不想说原来她什么也不是
Oh, I don't wanna say from nowhere,
但实际上
but that technically wouldn't be
这样的形容也不过分
the wrong address with her.
然后你出现了 给我好好讲讲
And then came you. Do tell.
也许 我是说也许 他们在其它地方也可以找到
And maybe, just maybe, they will find the strength
生活的力量
in other parts of their life as well.
否则他们就只会脸红和傻笑了
- Or they'll just blush and giggle.
稍后回来
We'll be right back.
看上去还不错嘛
So far, so good.
所以你们打算正式公开关系不
So are you guys going open and official?
秘密的办公室恋情哈 这次又有什么新戏码
Secret office romance? What's the play this time?
卡尔文怎么办 他可是做保险的
What about Calvin, huh? He had that sexy insurance job.
别说了 里奇
Snooze, Richie.
蒂娜需要的可不是人寿保险
Tina deserves more than life insurance.
她需要的是冒险
She deserves adventure.
那去和埃维尔·柯尼韦尔的海盗约会呗
So then date a pirate or Evel Knievel.
道格二者兼有
- Doug's kind of both.
我可能就喜欢这种便宜货色吧
I guess I like a cheap thrill.
我明白 但这次确实跟以往不同
I get it, but it really does feel different this time.
他的童年创伤都疗愈了
- Oh, so he's dealt with his childhood trauma?
他的两个前妻呢
His two ex-wives?
蒂娜 我只是希望你开心
Tina, I just wanna see you happy.
那就好 因为我很开心
Good, because I am.
你天生就是吃这碗饭的
You're a natural.
我之前不是在开玩笑 你很会说话
I wasn't joking before. You play your cards right,
你未来会有更多选择的
you're going to have options.
目前这样就行 谢了
That's good for now. Thanks.
纽约杂志社
我今早交的稿子
- I turned in my draft this morning.
嗯
Mm-hmm.
我通宵没睡修改的
I pulled an all-nighter polishing.
天哪 我都出汗了
Oh, God, I am sweating.
但我又浑身发冷 还恶心
I'm also cold, you know, and nauseated.
还眼冒金星
I'm seeing spots as well.
我真不该喝第二杯茶
I should not have had that second cup of tea.
给 吃点东西吧 你的肯定行
Here. Eat something. I'm sure it's great.
你跟那些笨蛋比 可比95%的人都要强
You are a better writer that 95% of these meatballs.
只要耐心等待
You know, it's only a matter of time
乔治一定会让你写署名文章的
before George gives you a byline.
你可不止是个研究员
You are so beyond a researcher.
-我们都是  -谢谢
- We both are. - Thank you.
只是
It's just--
实在猜不透他在想什么
it's so hard to tell what he's thinking, you know?
我跟他说我要写时他使劲鼓励我
He was profoundly encouraging when I told him that
但等我写完交给他时
I wanted to do it, but then when I turned it in--
他又摆出那副典型的不表态乔治的神情
He did that noncommittal George thing
特别安静 然后眼睛就一条缝
where he gets really quiet and his eyes narrow
你都不知道他是在想你的文章啊
and you can't tell if he's thinking about
-还是在想午饭吃什么  -我知道
- you or his lunch? - Yes.
男人特别擅长来这套
Men are so good at that.
我现在就想让别人看着我
All I want in life is for people to look at me,
然后也不知道我在想什么
have no idea what I'm thinking,
然后担心的要死
and then be really worried.
对 我觉得也是
Yeah. I think that's right.
稍微了解一下她
Just crop in on her a little bit.
确保我们能看到她的脸
And make sure that we can see her face.
谁不喜欢办公室的风流韵事呢
Who doesn't love a good office fling?
5 4
In five, four,
3 2
three, two--
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
我们谈论了女权主义和色情文学
We're talking about feminism and pornography,
而且还挺开心的
and we're having a good time.
我们聊得挺开心的对吧
We're having a good time, right?
非常开心 迪克
A great time Dick.
很高兴听到你这么说
So glad to hear it
我现在想扩展一下我们的对话
I wanna expand the conversation.
再请上一个客人来
Bring out another guest.
她应该是美国女性问题
She's probably America's foremost voice
最前卫的声音了
on women's issues.
一个作家 也是个倡导者
An author. An advocate.
她来我们这个节目几次了
She's been a guest here a number of times
是个非常聪明的女性
and just, well, a really smart lady.
有请 维多利亚·哈特尼特
Please welcome, Victoria Hartnett.
天哪
- Oh, my God.
天 我太荣幸了
Oh, my God. This is such an honor.
真的是
Really this is - wow.
大家看看哈
Oh, well, will you look at this?
我都不知道学者也有追星族呢
I didn't even know academics could have groupies.
我花了整个大四一年的时间
I've only spent my entire senior year
反复拜读了
reading and rereading
《重访巴比伦的妓女》
"The Whore of Babylon Revisited."
那本书实在是
Oh. - That work is just--
-太有创意了  -谢谢
- it's seminal. - Thank you.
为了写那本书我都离婚了
It cost me my first marriage, so I'm glad someone
所以我很高兴还有人能从里面看出点积极的东西来
got something positive out of it.
我邀请维多利亚来是因为
I brought Victoria on because, you know,
我们想多听听不同的观点
we like to have a variety of viewpoints.
让我们的对话更有趣
Makes for more interesting conversation.
我先问这个吧 你觉得《风骚女子》如何
And, well, let me just ask, what do you think of "Minx"?
首先 我想说 我钦佩任何
Well, first of all, let me say I admire
推动社会对女性认识的行为
any woman who pushes society's expectations
让社会了解她们能做什么 不能做什么
of what they can and cannot do or be,
-所以 很棒  -谢谢
- so brava. - Thank you.
但是我认为像《风骚女子》这种杂志
But I think a magazine like "Minx"
对于我们的大业是有害的 甚至可以说是阴险的
is harmful to the cause, maybe even a little insidious.
我们这个国家 甚至全世界
We have a serious agenda for women
-对于女性都有非常严肃的计划  -绝对是
- in this nation, on this planet. - Absolutely.
那为什么我们还要喋喋不休地
Then why are we blathering about
聊丁丁和色情文学呢
penises and pornographers?
我 杂志写的都是很严肃的问题
I-- I write about critical issues.
没错 可只是流于表面
Yes, you do, superficially.
即便如此 也都淹没在色情的海洋之中了
But even that is drowned in a sea of salaciousness.
色情吗
Salaciousness?
我承认里面有几张裸体照片
There are a few naked pictures, sure,
但是也有很多严肃的内容
but there are pages and pages of serious content.
听我说 亲爱的
Listen, my dear,
我确定你的心是好的
I'm sure your heart is in the right place
我也不想把你称为受害者
and I wouldn't call you a victim
但从某种程度上来说 你被利用了
but, in a sense, you have been used.
这可能就是为什么人会说
This might be why they say you don't wanna
-不要见自己的偶像吧  -你在帮倒忙 迪克
- meet your heroes. Not helpful, Dick.
你杂志的内容是一个非常聪明的
Your content is cover
商人在为自己打掩护
for a very clever businessman
以扩展自己的业务到一个尚未开发的巨大色情市场
to expand into an enormous untapped market for pornography
向女性出售香烟 酒精和汽车
to sell cigarettes and alcohol and automobiles to women.
雪上加霜的是
And to add insult to injury,
你虽然被聘为编辑
you've been hired as editor
但只是被赋予了有控制权的错觉
but only been given the illusion of control.
我不知道怎么 但不是
I don't know what-- no. Okay, no.
我是说 这本杂志是我的
I mean, look, the magazine is mine.
你的出版商
Mm, your publisher might
可能对此会持不同意见
have a different opinion on that.
我们的对话很明显越来越刺激了
Well, this conversation has certainly gotten spicier.
我们先短暂休息一下
We're gonna take a quick break
看看是否能解决这个问题
and see if we can't sort this all out.
-怎么回事道格  -我不知道
- What is going on here, Doug? - I don't know.
我不知道她在说什么
I don't know what she's talking about.
但你只要坚持下去就好 淡定点
But just stay in it. Stay calm.
别上她的当 做出反击
Don't take the bait and counterpunch.
我又不是拳击手
But I'm not some pugilist.
这是我的职业生涯 我的人生 而她
This is my life here. My work. And she's--
普里格小姐 嗨 我们需要给你
- Miss Prigger, hi. We need you for some
-迅速补个妆  -不用了 我不
touch-ups real quick. - No, I'm fine. I don't--
你脸上会有汗
Just a small sweat issue.
当灯光变热时
You know, the camera adds a bit of a glimmer
摄像机照在脸上会有点反光
when the lights get hot. - Oh.
加油 加油啊
- Stay in the fight. Stay in the fight.
-雷内蒂先生  -嗯
- Mr. Renetti? - Yeah.
我们的监制想跟您聊两句
Can our producer talk to you for a second?
-行 行  -欢迎回来
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. - Welcome back.
我们刚才就裸体男人的话题进行了
We've been having a spirited conversation
一场精彩的对话
about naked men.
天 有时候这工作还真是挺奇妙的
Boy, this is a weird job sometimes.
那么一本充斥着裸体男性的杂志到底是女权主义的体现
Is a magazine full of them a feminist act
还是个恶毒的分散女人注意力的伎俩
or just a nasty ploy to distract the ladies,
只为了让她们停止要求加薪之类的
get them to stop asking for raises and stuff?
虽然过于简约 迪克 但意思没错
Reductive, Dick, but not inaccurate.
《风骚女子》的男性出版商
The male publisher of "Minx"
在对话中出现了几次
has come up a few times in conversation.
他今晚也在 我想把他也请上来
He's here tonight. I wanna have him out
看看他对此有什么话好说
and see what he has to say.
欢迎道格·J·雷内蒂
Please welcome Douglas J. Renetti.
真荣幸
What an honor.
这位先生的步伐真是很有活力啊
Someone's got some pep in his step.
能来这我很激动 我爱纽约
Well, I'm excited to be here. I love New York.
它的能量 它的土地 它所有的一切
The energy, the dirt, all of it.
你去过时代广场吗
Have you been to Times Square?
在你们这行混的我觉得
A man in your profession might need to,
有必要去窥一下竞争情况
I wanna say "peep" the competition.
你真风趣 不 我是出差过来的
Very funny. No, I come here on business.
见见广告商什么的
Meeting with advertisers, that sort of thing.
你一直在成人娱乐界吗
- And have you always been in adult entertainment?
并非如此 我开始是靠剪息票起家的
No, I started with a few penny savers, coupon clippers.
然后我看到了市场的机会 于是就贷了款
And I saw an opportunity, so I got a small loan
一点点把生意做起来
and I busted my butt, title by title.
你现在看到的就是真人版的美国之梦
You're looking at the American dream, Dick,
迪克
in the flesh. - Oh, wow.
我自己都说不出这种话
I couldn't have said it better myself.
真希望我能
Kind of wish I did.
你应该也听到我们刚才的对话了
Now, you've been following our conversation.
那你们的杂志到底是谁在负责呢 你还是乔伊斯
Just who's in control of your magazine, you, Joyce?
我们是合作伙伴关系
- Well, we share a dynamic partnership.
乔伊斯应该也会这么说
I think Joyce would say the same thing.
在底袋钱 我们用的是“全员参与”的理念来经营的
At Bottom Dollar, we share an "all hands on deck" philosophy.
-对吧  -没错
- Right? - Yup.
但是他会知道适可而止
But the buck has gotta stop somewhere.
道格从来不会越界干涉杂志的编辑
Doug would never overstep into editorial, no.
跟所有出版商一样 他会出建议
He has suggestions, like all publishers,
但《风骚女子》是由我来管理的
but "Minx" is under my direction.
哈 雷内蒂先生刚才在后台
Huh. Mr. Renetti was actually regaling me backstage
有跟我分享解决你杂志未来问题的计划呢
with plans for a future issue for your magazine.
别瞎说
Stop it now.
我们只是以专业人士的角度讨论了一下而已
We were just gabbing pro to pro. You know it.
别谦虚了 雷内蒂先生
Don't play humble now, Mr. Renetti.
你当时可是非常非常自豪
You were very, very proud.
你甚至还笑容满面地提到了下一期杂志的封面
You were beaming, even, about your next cover.
不 我们下期杂志的
Oh, no. We have not settled
封面还没有定
on the cover for our next issue, no.
没错 我们还没定
That's correct. No, we haven't.
只是前期阶段
We are in the early stages,
讨论了一些人选
just talking to people.
我们超喜欢这对话的进展
Well, we love process here.
愿意看到这香肠是如何做出来的
Love to see how the sausage gets made.
抱歉 我忍不住想用这个词
I'm sorry. I couldn't help it.
-我只是  -没事 没事
- I'm just a-- - That was good. That was good.
我就是个喜剧人物
Comic at heart, people.
下面的观众中正好有几位
But we also happen to have quite a few readers
是你们杂志的读者
in the audience-- people who might be
他们对你们的现状很感兴趣
interested in what you have on tap.
除非你不喜欢免费的广告 雷内蒂先生
Unless you don't like free advertising, Mr. Renetti.
你知道我喜欢免费广告
- Oh, you know I love free advertising.
感谢各位读者
And thank you to all the readers.
可我们现在还没有什么能跟大家分享的
There's nothing to-- to share right now.
也许我们能透露
Perhaps we could let the cat out of the bag
-一点点可  -我们还没有准备好
- a little bit. - There's no cat.
就假设 我们已经有内容了
Considering-- there might be a cat.
有让大家十分惊喜的内容
There might be a big cat.
我可以给你来面鼓 你要鼓吗
- I can get you a drumroll. Do you wanna a drumroll?
-没有  -来吧
- No. - Yeah.
-不 我们不需要鼓  -鲍比 敲鼓吧
- No. We don't need a drumroll. - Bobby, hit it!
道格 你不需要鼓
Doug, you don't need a drumroll.
-我也不需要  -他不需要
- I don't need a drumroll. - He doesn't need a drumroll
因为没有什么可以透露的
'cause there's nothing to reveal.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen!
下期《风骚女子》杂志的封面人物
In the next "Minx" and on the cover,
将是赢得所有荣耀的
posing in all his God-given glory
美国最受欢迎的四分卫比利·布伦森
will be America's favorite quarterback,
历史最佳球员
Billy Brunson, "The GOAT"!
我们请到了比利·布伦森
We got Billy Brunson!
没错啦
We got him.
太让人激动了
- Wow. This is exciting.
-你们在这里首次听到了这个消息  -还有 还有其它
- And you heard it here first. - There's--there's other--
就像我常说的 最好的真相都是赤裸裸的
Like I always say, the best truths are naked ones.
他们成长的好快啊
- Oh, wow. They grow up so fast.
最新的激进分子跟原来一样吗
嗑药不扔炸弹
没什么大不了的
It's no big deal.
麦克奈特先生 占据封面文章的最年轻的作家
- Mr. McKnight, youngest writer ever to land a cover.
有人真的做到了啊
Someone has indubitably made it.
让我看看 让我看看
Let me see that. Let me see.
传过来看看
Pass it around. Pass it around.
亲爱的 这也不算太糟糕
Sweetie, it's not all bad news.
你的努力方向是对的
You were obviously on the right track.
他们用了你的想法
They used your idea. Sort of.
一篇精心布局的
A thoughtful, original article
关于正在发展的厌女症的原创文章
about misogyny in the movement
已经被幻化成
has been transmogrified into this
一个精英的拍马屁式的侧写
pat profile of cavalier elites
由某个根本不在场的
written by some cavalier elite
所谓的精英撰写
who wasn't even there,
他们都没有去捡鸡蛋
who didn't have to get the eggs!
鸡舍听起来是挺吓人的
The hen house does sound terrifying.
但这个杂志社不在乎这些细节
This magazine is not interested in those details.
不过既然你能在这混下去
But you survive here,
你就一定能有所作为
it just might get you to someplace that is.
他都没有跟我任何反馈
He didn't even give me any feedback.
他就 他就直接拿去用了
You know, he just-he just took it
还把它篡改成一篇完全不同的文章
and he just made it into something else.
天 我真是个傻子
God, I'm such an idiot.
我要跟他谈谈去
I'm gonna talk to him.
乔伊斯
- Oh, Joyce.
给你在途中准备了一点小礼物
A little something for the road ahead.
你没必要这样的
Oh. You shouldn't have.
我让弗朗辛去的
I sent Francine.
嘿 我知道你在怪我
Hey, before you say anything,
-但我当时也是没办法  -随便吧
- I was backed into a corner. - Yeah, right.
整件事情都是事先准备好的 道格 你可真会做秀啊
The whole thing was staged. Great television, Doug.
在洛杉矶时他们就告诉你维多利亚·哈特尼特要来吧
When did they tell you about Victoria Hartnett, back in LA?
你说什么呢
- What are you talking about?
我一点都不知道
I didn't know anything about it.
行吧 然后还有比利的事
- Okay. And then the Billy bomb.
-也是脱口而出的哈  -就是
- Completely spontaneous. - Yes, it was.
现场的灯光 人们都在盯着你 还有乐队
You got the lights, you got people staring, the band.
可是管弦乐队啊 乔伊斯
He's got an orchestra, Joyce.
我能怎么做 真的什么都不说吗
What I'm gonna do, say no to a drumroll?
没人那么做过
No one's ever done that ever.
道格·雷内蒂 就是
Doug Renetti, a leaf on a stream
人在江湖身不由己是吧
being merrily carried along.
谁知道接下来会发生什么
"Ooh, wherever will it take me next?"
我搞砸了 行吗
I screwed up, okay?
但我发誓 我不知道有关特邀嘉宾的任何内幕
But I swear I didn't know anything about the other guest.
-那比利呢  -好吧
- Oh, please. And Billy? - Fine.
我和前的一位公关联系了一下
I took a flyer with an old PR contact
和比利见了个面
and I got a meeting with Billy, okay?
但是我不认为比利会来
But I did not think that Billy was gonna show.
我绝对没想到他会答应
And I definitely didn't think he was gonna say yes.
这是真的
And that's the truth.
我知道 没跟你商量就做这事是我不对
It was wrong of me to do any of this without consulting you.
你做的所有事都是错的
It was wrong of you to do any of this, period!
像你这种人 就像是日蚀
You know, men like you, you're an eclipse.
你也没想这么做 但你就是忍不住
You don't mean to do it but you can't help
-一定要遮住太阳  -怎么 你现在是太阳了是吗
but just block out the sun! - Oh, so you're the sun now?
滋润万物是吧
You're the giver of life?
乔伊斯 我给你说吧
Joyce, let me explain something to you.
我们现在热度正高
We are on an incredible hot streak.
第三期杂志的发行量
Out third issue is gonna have
将在所有杂志中排名第11位
the 11th highest circulation of any magazine.
-多亏了谁  -让我说完
Yes, thanks to whom? - Let me finish!
多亏了我的努力 多亏了我
Thanks to my work. Thanks to my work.
三期
Three issues!
乔伊斯 我们在影响这个行业
We are changing the game, Joyce.
我不会因为自己是个全明星运动员
And I'm not gonna apologize to you or to anybody
就对你或者任何人觉得抱歉
for playing it like a goddamn all-star.
如果你不喜欢我的这个类比 不好意思
And if you don't like my sports analogy, tough shit.
我的杂志
It's my ball.
我的规矩 你明白了吗
My rules. You get it?
行吧
Yeah.
这是你出版第三期《风骚女子》杂志的所有资料
This is everything you'll need for issue three of "Minx,"
除了中间插页
save for the centerfold,
反正你也想好用什么了
which you have already taken care of.
我想这样也符合我们的协议吧
I believe that fulfills the terms of our agreement.
站住 你不能就这样离开吧
Stop it. You're not leaving like this.
-你那么在意  -我以为我做了那么多
- You care too much. - I thought I had done enough
应该赢得了你的尊重 但是我不会
to earn your respect, but I will not allow
让人这样对我的 再也不能这样了
people to treat me this way. Not anymore.
听我说 乔
Listen, J--
-我来吧 剩下的交给我  -好
- I got it. I'll do the rest. - Okay.
-确定  -嗯
- You sure? - Yeah.
-我爱你  -我也爱你
- Love you. - You too.
-不会有事的对吧  -嗯
- It'll be fine, right? - Sure.